Guide to the Chard Powers Smith Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1901-1978; Series I; 21.27; (51 boxes)
  - General Correspondence, 1910-1978
    - Holle, Murray, 1942 September 2 (Box 18, Folder 711)
    - Hollman, Albert, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 712)
    - Holly, Flora M., 1946 (Box 18, Folder 713)
    - Hollywood Cemetery Co., 1951 March 5 (Box 18, Folder 714)
    - Holmes, John, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 715)
    - Holt, Barbara, 1963-1973 (Box 18, Folder 716)
    - Holt, Rhinehart and Winston, Inc., 1960-1972 (Box 18, Folder 717)
    - Honor, James, 1958 February 22 (Box 18, Folder 718)
    - Hooker, James Louis, undated (Box 18, Folder 719)
    - Horan, Frank, 1940-1967, undated (Box 18, Folder 720)
    - The Hotchkiss Library; Sharon, Conn., 1942-1944 (Box 18, Folder 721)
    - Hotel Pennsylvania, 1950 December 29 (Box 18, Folder 722)
    - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1928-1972 (Box 18, Folder 723-724)
    - Houghton, Walter L., 1939 October 30 (Box 18, Folder 725)
    - Houlé, Maud Tillotson, 1946 August 17 (Box 18, Folder 726)
    - Housatonic Bookshop, 1944-1945, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 727)
    - Housatonic River Improvement Association of Berkshire County, 1945 June 20 (Box 18, Folder 728)
    - Howard, Clare E., 1925 May 25 (Box 18, Folder 729)
    - Howard, Eunice, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 730)
    - Howard, Sidney, 1935-1936 (Box 18, Folder 731)
    - Howe Caverns, Inc., 1939 October 25 (Box 18, Folder 732)
    - Howe, Irving, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 733)
    - Howe, Mary, 1946, undated (Box 18, Folder 734)
    - Howell, A. C., 1923 October 22 (Box 18, Folder 735)
    - Howell, Rlene, undated (Box 18, Folder 736)
    - Hubbard, Lydia Brewster, 1942 January 21 (Box 18, Folder 737)
    - Hubbell, M. R., 1942 (Box 18, Folder 738)
    - Hubbell, Taylor, Goodwin, Nixon & Hargrave, 1932-1939 (Box 18, Folder 739)
    - Huchting, Fritz, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 740)
    - Huessy, Eugene Rosenstock, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 741)
    - Hughes, Grace, undated (Box 18, Folder 742)
    - Hughes, Hatcher, 1936 (Box 18, Folder 743)
    - Hughes, Kacy, undated (Box 18, Folder 744)
    - Humphrey, Peggy, undated (Box 18, Folder 745)
    - Hungerford, Edward, 1939 November 2 (Box 18, Folder 746)
    - The Hungerford-Holbrook Company Printers, 1935 August 3 (Box 18, Folder 747)
    - Hunn, Hiram, 1970 December 24 (Box 18, Folder 748)
    - Hunting, Maro S. (Bunny), 1910-1939 (Box 18, Folder 749-750)
    - Huntington Hartford Foundation, 1955-1960 (Box 18, Folder 751)
    - Hurd, Betty, 1974 August 15 (Box 18, Folder 752)
    - Hurd, Edna, 1940 January 12 (Box 18, Folder 753)
    - Hurd, Harry Elmore, 1935 April 5 (Box 18, Folder 754)
    - Hurlburt, Margaret, 1973 December 31 (Box 18, Folder 755)
    - Hurter, Janet, 1926-1939 (Box 18, Folder 756)
    - Hyde, George (Ted) and Norma, 1925-1974 (Box 18, Folder 757)
    - Hysham, Julie, undated (Box 18, Folder 758)
    - Illif Review, 1968 May 3 (Box 19, Folder 759)
    - Ill Health Club, 1913 December 15 (Box 19, Folder 760)
    - The Independent, 1924 June 20 (Box 19, Folder 761)
    - Indiana University Press, 1960-1971 (Box 19, Folder 762)
    - Informative Classroom Picture Publishers, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 763)
    - Ingalls, Jeremy, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 764)
    - Inglehart, George G., 1935-1965 (Box 19, Folder 765)
    - Inglehart, Nina C., 1965 July 12 (Box 19, Folder 766)
    - International P. E. N., 1965 June 8 (Box 19, Folder 767)
    - Italian Representative to the United Nations, 1954 February 19 (Box 19, Folder 768)
    - Ives, Dorothy M., 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 769)
    - Ives Washburn, Inc., 1959 (Box 19, Folder 770)
    - Izant, Betty, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 771)
    - "J" General, 1911-1963 (Box 19, Folder 772)
    - J.B. Lippincott Company, 1958-1970 (Box 19, Folder 773)
    - Jackson, B. W., 1963 May 13 (Box 19, Folder 774)
    - Jackson, Joseph Henry, 1941-1952 (Box 19, Folder 775)
    - Jackson, Kay, 1943-1949 (Box 19, Folder 776)
    - Jackson, William A., 1962-1964 (Box 19, Folder 777)
    - James, Ben, 1940 December 11 (Box 19, Folder 778)
    - James, Kelly, 1964 October 17 (Box 19, Folder 779)
    - Jarmel, Doyle, 1951 January 19 (Box 19, Folder 780)
    - Jarmel, Faie, 1924 April 10 (Box 19, Folder 781)
    - Jaschinsky, Emma, undated (Box 19, Folder 782)
    - Jasmine, Paul, 1953-1954 (Box 19, Folder 783)
    - Jeffers, Robinson and Una, 1934-1936 (Box 19, Folder 784)
    - Jefferson County Historical Society, 1941-1965 (Box 19, Folder 785)
    - Jefferson County National Bank, 1940 December 17 (Box 19, Folder 786)
    - Jenkins, Edwin T., 1945 (Box 19, Folder 787)
    - Jennings, Les, 1932, undated (Box 19, Folder 788)
    - Jennings, Vera, 1928-1940 (Box 19, Folder 789)
    - John Cushman Associates, Inc., 1966 July 18 (Box 19, Folder 790)
    - Johns, Josephine, 1965 September 3 (Box 19, Folder 791)
    - Johnson, Agnes W., 1943-1944 (Box 19, Folder 792)
    - Johnson, Alvin, 1931-1936 (Box 19, Folder 793)
    - Johnson, Harold B., 1935-1940 (Box 19, Folder 794)
    - Johnson, Rita, undated (Box 19, Folder 795)
    - Johnston, Julia E., 1935-1936 (Box 19, Folder 796)
    - Joio, Norman Dello, 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 797)
    - Jones, Elizabeth, 1946 March 11 (Box 19, Folder 798)
    - Jones, Gary M., 1916 July1 (Box 19, Folder 799)
    - Jones, H. M., 1945-1948 (Box 19, Folder 800)
    - Jones, Howard, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 801)
    - Jones, Lou Belle, 1928-1941 (Box 19, Folder 802-803)
    - Jones, S. M., 1945 May 11 (Box 19, Folder 804)
    - Jordan-Smith, Paul, 1939-1965 (Box 19, Folder 805-806)
    - Jurgen, Robert J., 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 807)
    - "K" General, 1961-1972 (Box 20, Folder 808)
    - Kane, Amanda, 1937 January 15 (Box 20, Folder 809)
    - Katz, Joseph P., 1940 June 9 (Box 20, Folder 810)
    - Kays, Mary, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 811)
    - Keedick, Lee, 1946 August 12 (Box 20, Folder 812)
    - Keen, Sam, 1973 April 26 (Box 20, Folder 813)
    - Kendall, George M., 1961-1971 (Box 20, Folder 814)
    - Kennebec County, Maine, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 815)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1962 January 7 (Box 20, Folder 816)
      Outgoing only.
      See also: Moore, Hugh
    - Kennefick, ----, 1952 September 19 (Box 20, Folder 817)
    - Kennikat Press, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 818)
    - Kent Art Association, 1950 May 29 (Box 20, Folder 819)
    - Kent, Fay Barnaby, 1965 September 30 (Box 20, Folder 820)
    - Kent, Sarah, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 821)
    - Kentworthy, Leonard S., 1971 February 2 (Box 20, Folder 822)
    - Keskiner, Peg, 1970, undated (Box 20, Folder 823)
    - Keyes, Rowena Keith, 1946 September 16 (Box 20, Folder 824)
    - Kimball, Jessie, 1910-1911 (Box 20, Folder 825)
    - King, Robert F., 1930-1943 (Box 20, Folder 826)
    - King, Spencer, 1961 January 20 (Box 20, Folder 827)
    - Kinsolving, Sally, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 828)
    - Kleeman, Rita Halle, 1965 September 30 (Box 20, Folder 829)
    - Klein, Jacob, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 830)
    - Klein, Norman, 1947 March 14 (Box 20, Folder 831)
    - Knapp, Farwell, 1925-1939 (Box 20, Folder 832)
    - Knapp, Marjorie, 1925-1947 (Box 20, Folder 833)
    - Knapp, Wilhelmina, 1934 May 19 (Box 20, Folder 834)
    - The Knickerbocker News, 1965 December 11 (Box 20, Folder 835)
    - Kowlton, C. M., 1928 April 25 (Box 20, Folder 836)
    - Knowlton, T. E. and Katharina, 1928-1939 (Box 20, Folder 837)
    - Knubel, Helen M., 1947 July 22 (Box 20, Folder 838)
    - Kouvel, Audrey, 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 839)
    - Kramer, Gretchen, 1935 May 22 (Box 20, Folder 840)
    - Kreymborg, Alfred, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 841)
    - Kubik, Gail, 1947 August 23 (Box 20, Folder 842)
    - Kunkel, Beverly, 1934-1935 (Box 20, Folder 843)
    - Kunkel, Sally, undated (Box 20, Folder 844)
    - "L" General, 1940-1965 (Box 20, Folder 845)
    - L----, Sally G., undated (Box 20, Folder 846)
    - Labbie, John and Edith, 1962-1965 (Box 20, Folder 847)
    - Lacey, Paul A., 1963 July 31 (Box 20, Folder 848)
    - LaFarge, Christopher, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 849)
    - LaFarge, Mrs. Thomas, 1943, undated (Box 20, Folder 850)
    - Laidlaw, Harriet, 1935-1936 (Box 20, Folder 851)
    - Lamb, Halley Anne, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 852)
    - Lambert, Jean, 1959 May 26 (Box 20, Folder 853)
    - Lampson, Robin, 1935-1936 (Box 20, Folder 854)
    - Landeck, Armin, 1945-1969, undated (Box 20, Folder 855)
    - Langstroth, Ivan, 1940 August 21 (Box 20, Folder 856)
    - Lansing, A. T. E., 1952, undated (Box 20, Folder 857)
    - Lansing, Edward, 1910-1929 (Box 20, Folder 858)
    - Lansing, Emma Sterling, 1935 October 18 (Box 20, Folder 859)
    - Lansing, Grace Moffett, 1923 August 13 (Box 20, Folder 860)
    - Latham, Harold S., 1935-1961 (Box 20, Folder 861)
    - Laments, D. M., 1950 (Box 20, Folder 862)
    - Lay, Charles Downing, 1942 (Box 20, Folder 863)
    - Leach, Henry G., 1935 April 9 (Box 20, Folder 864)
    - League of American Writers, 1939-1940 (Box 20, Folder 865)
    - Leaky, Louis S. B., 1965 (Box 21, Folder 866)
    - Leathers, Lyman, 1963-1967 (Box 21, Folder 867)
    - Ledoux & Company, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 868)
    - Lee, H. and J., 1972 January 13 (Box 21, Folder 869)
    - Lee, H. Chong, 1965 February 23 (Box 21, Folder 870)
    - Lee, Harry O., 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 871)
    - Lee, Lawrence, 1932 October 20 (Box 21, Folder 872)
    - Lee Library Association, 1942-1946 (Box 21, Folder 873)
    - Lee, R. E., 1927 August 30 (Box 21, Folder 874)
    - Lee, Robert, 1956-1965 (Box 21, Folder 875)
    - Leggett, John, 1965-1969 (Box 21, Folder 876)
    - Leisy, Dr. E. E., 1950 (Box 21, Folder 877)
    - Lemau, May, 1940 January 11 (Box 21, Folder 878)
    - Lennon, Florence Becker, 1963-1965 (Box 21, Folder 879)
    - Lenox Library Association, 1942-1946 (Box 21, Folder 880)
    - Lenskins, U. W., 1926 August 1 (Box 21, Folder 881)
    - Lespined, Sarah P., undated (Box 21, Folder 882)
    - Levy, Jeff, 1950 March 3 (Box 21, Folder 883)
    - Lewis, Martin, 1943 January 9 (Box 21, Folder 884)
    - Library of Congress, 1955-1973 (Box 21, Folder 885)
    - Liddy, Ola Irene, 1936 September 22 (Box 21, Folder 886)
    - Lieb, Henrietta, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 887)
    - Lincoln County, Maine, 1963 May 8 (Box 21, Folder 888)
    - Linde, Philip N., 1965 (Box 21, Folder 889)
    - Lindley, S. Wolcott, 1947 January 15 (Box 21, Folder 890)
    - Litchfield Enquirer Publishing Company, 1935 April 3 (Box 21, Folder 891)
    - The Literary Review, 1960-1968 (Box 21, Folder 892)
    - Little, "Binks", 1968 (Box 21, Folder 893)
    - Little, Brown and Company, 1958-1965 (Box 21, Folder 894)
    - Little, Royal, 1950 April 15 (Box 21, Folder 895)
    - Littlefield, Tom, 1967 October 9 (Box 21, Folder 896)
    - Lloyd, Bishop, 1932 (Box 21, Folder 897)
    - Logan, Robert, 1957-1968 (Box 21, Folder 898)
    - Logan, Sheriden, 1953 April 3 (Box 21, Folder 899)
    - The London Mercury, 1927-1929 (Box 21, Folder 900)
    - Long, Beth, 1973 November 1 (Box 21, Folder 901)
    - Long, H., undated (Box 21, Folder 902)
    - Long, Ham, undated (Box 21, Folder 903)
    - Longfellow, Robert E., 1935 November 18 (Box 21, Folder 904)
    - Lord, Alice Frost, 1937 May 25 (Box 21, Folder 905)
    - Lowell, Robert, 1959-1967 (Box 21, Folder 906)
    - Lovett, Paul, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 907)
    - Lovitt, William, 1959-1960 (Box 21, Folder 908)
    - Lowell, Amy, 1925 January 30 (Box 21, Folder 909)
    - Lucas, Pearl, 1968, undated (Box 21, Folder 910)
    - Lufkin, Charles T., 1952 February 28 (Box 21, Folder 911)
    - Luke, Matthew and Charmion, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 912)
    - Lukens, Russell N., 1939 November 1 (Box 21, Folder 913)
    - Lyon, Robert, 1952 March 13 (Box 21, Folder 914)
    - "M" General, 1911-1966 (Box 22, Folder 915)
    - M----, C., 1923 April 5 (Box 22, Folder 916)
    - McAskill, Edith S., 1935 October 9 (Box 22, Folder 917)
    - McCabe, Jim, 1960 March 23 (Box 22, Folder 918)
    - McCall, Marcia, 1965 August 17 (Box 22, Folder 919)
    - McCaw, Marguerite, 1941 October 28 (Box 22, Folder 920)
    - McClaughy, John, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 921)
    - McClelland, David C., 1963 (Box 22, Folder 922)
    - McCluggage, Denise, 1968 June 18 (Box 22, Folder 923)
    - McConaughy, James L., 1939-1946 (Box 22, Folder 924)
    - McCormick, Ada P., 1948 (Box 22, Folder 925)
    - McCracken, Henry Hoble, 1936 July 9 (Box 22, Folder 926)
    - McCumber, S. S., 1936-1939 (Box 22, Folder 927)
    - MacDonald & Co. LTD, 1954-1969 (Box 22, Folder 928-930)
    - MacDonald, Dwight, 1965 January 16 (Box 22, Folder 931)
    - MacDonald, Peter, 1944 September 8 (Box 22, Folder 932)
    - MacDowell Association, 1948-1970 (Box 22, Folder 933-934)
    - The MacDowell Colonists, 1950-1971 (Box 22, Folder 935)
    - The MacDowell Colony, 1950-1970 (Box 22, Folder 936-937)
    - MacDowell, Marian, 1924-1951 (Box 22, Folder 938)
    - McDuffie, Erika, 1962 December 2 (Box 22, Folder 939)
    - McGrayne, Ruth, 1938-1959 (Box 22, Folder 940)
    - McIntosh & Otis, Inc., 1941-1971 (Box 22, Folder 941)
    - MacIntosh, Mavis, 1950-1954 (Box 22, Folder 942)
    - MacKaye, Mary M., 1965 March 9 (Box 22, Folder 943)
    - McKee, Lulu, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 944)
    - McKillop, Margaret K., 1942 (Box 22, Folder 945)
    - McKinley, Georgia, 1967-1969 (Box 22, Folder 946)
    - MacLachlan, John, 1927 June 2 (Box 22, Folder 947)
    - McLane, Allan, 1928-1929 (Box 22, Folder 948)
    - McLean, Ken, 1950-1953 (Box 22, Folder 949)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, 1933-1969 (Box 22, Folder 950)
    - McLester, J. C., 1939 (Box 22, Folder 951)
    - McManus, Pat, 1962-1964, undated (Box 22, Folder 952)
    - MacMillan Company, 1935-1968 (Box 23, Folder 953-961)
    - MacMillan, W. D., 1932 October 19 (Box 23, Folder 962)
    - Magee, Ralph W., 1936 July 22 (Box 24, Folder 963)
    - Maine. Bureau of Inland Fisheries, 1968 May 23 (Box 24, Folder 964)
    - Malamud, Bernard, 1963-1967 (Box 24, Folder 965)
    - Malcolm, Ted, 1931 (Box 24, Folder 966)
    - Mallam, Phosphor, 1926 (Box 24, Folder 967)
    - Mallary, Richard W., 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 968)
    - Mallikjees, Gurdial, 1963 September 30 (Box 24, Folder 969)
    - Magravite, Peppino, 1970 May 15 (Box 24, Folder 970)
    - March, Florence Eldridge, undated (Box 24, Folder 971)
    - Marlboro College, 1949-1950 (Box 24, Folder 972)
    - Marsh, Emily E., 1945 (Box 24, Folder 973)
    - Marsh, Frederick, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 974)
    - Marsh, Norman J., 1949-1964 (Box 24, Folder 975)
    - Martin, Gordon, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 976)
    - Martin, John Stuart, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 977)
    - Masefield, John, 1921 July 25 (Box 24, Folder 978)
    - Mason, Rodney, 1929, undated (Box 24, Folder 979)
    - The Massachusetts Review, 1961-1968 (Box 24, Folder 980-981)
    - Massey, ----, 1959 January 12 (Box 24, Folder 982)
    - Mathewson, William A., 1966 March 15 (Box 24, Folder 983)
    - Mavis McIntosh - Elizabeth McKee, Literary Representatives, 1951-1956 (Box 24, Folder 984)
    - Meadowcroft, Clara, 1936-1937 (Box 24, Folder 985)
    - Menconi, Ralph J., 1970 October 27 (Box 24, Folder 986)
    - Mensah-Dapaa, W. S., 1971 September 29 (Box 24, Folder 987)
    - Meridian Books, 1959 September 20 (Box 24, Folder 988)
    - Merriam, Albert C., 1962 October 24 (Box 24, Folder 989)
    - Merriam, Daniel, 1951-1952 (Box 24, Folder 990)
    - Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer Corporation, 1936 January 21 (Box 24, Folder 991)
    - Micklejohn, Helen, 1936, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 992)
    - Miller, A. J., 1946 July 12 (Box 24, Folder 993)
    - Miller, Arthur, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 994)
    - Miller, Doris Furnside, 1946 July 15 (Box 24, Folder 995)
    - Miller, Gina, 1939 November 4 (Box 24, Folder 996)
    - Miller, Perry, 1946-1949 (Box 24, Folder 997)
    - Miller, Pete, 1961-1965 (Box 24, Folder 998)
    - Miller, Sidney T., 1935 (Box 24, Folder 999)
    - Millett, Fred B., 1964-1967 (Box 24, Folder 1000)
    - Millican, C. Boure, 1932 October 23 (Box 24, Folder 1001)
    - Millington, Emily, 1926 July 20 (Box 24, Folder 1002)
    - Mills, Esther T., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 1003)
    - The Menaret, 1925 April 24 (Box 24, Folder 1004)
    - Mirick, Edith, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 1005)
    - Mittens, Eleanor, undated (Box 24, Folder 1006)
    - Modern Language Association of America, 1960 February 3 (Box 24, Folder 1007)
    - Moha, Datta, 19701974 (Box 24, Folder 1008)
    - Monroe, Fran, 1926 July 21 (Box 24, Folder 1009)
    - Monroe, Harriet, 1924 (Box 24, Folder 1010)
    - Montague, Margaret, 1926-1929 (Box 24, Folder 1011)
    - Montague, R. W., 1934-1936 (Box 24, Folder 1012)
    - Monteux, Pierre, 1951 January 3 (Box 24, Folder 1013)
    - Moore, Ann Leslie, 1962 April 14 (Box 24, Folder 1014)
    - Moore, Douglas, 1925-1949 (Box 24, Folder 1015)
    - Moore, Edmund H., 1953-1955 (Box 24, Folder 1016)
    - Moore, Hugh, 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 1017)
      See also: Kennedy, John F.
    - Moore, John G., 1937 June 3 (Box 24, Folder 1018)
    - Moore, Virginia, 1936 (Box 24, Folder 1019)
    - Morley, Blythe, 1949, undated (Box 24, Folder 1020)
    - Morris, ----, 1949 July 27 (Box 24, Folder 1021)
    - Morris, Lloyd, 1929 (Box 24, Folder 1022)
    - Morrison, Edward and Mabel, 1938-1943 (Box 24, Folder 1023)
    - Morrison, Samuel, 1954-1956 (Box 24, Folder 1024)
    - Morton, David, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 1025)
    - Morton, Marcus Jr., 1939, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 1026)
    - Mosaire, Jack W., undated (Box 25, Folder 1027)
    - Mosle, Henry B., 1941 November 15 (Box 25, Folder 1028)
    - Moss, Arnold, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 1029)
    - Motion Picture Society for the Americas, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 1030)
    - Mount Washington Public Library, 1942-1946 (Box 25, Folder 1031)
      Includes: Hunt, Nellie Jo
      Includes: Kreidemaker, Mildred
    - Mower, George R., 1968 February 3 (Box 25, Folder 1032)
    - Mueller, Oscar O., 1926 July 1 (Box 25, Folder 1033)
    - Mulligan, Louise E., 1973 (Box 25, Folder 1034)
    - Munger, Robert, undated (Box 25, Folder 1035)
    - Munson, Gorham, 1952 September 24 (Box 25, Folder 1036)
    - Murray, Henry A., 1946 July 19 (Box 25, Folder 1037)
    - Muskie, Edmund S., 1970 August 20 (Box 25, Folder 1038)
    - Myers, Eloise, 1942 November 5 (Box 25, Folder 1039)
    - Myers, John Myers, and Sky, 1958-1969 (Box 25, Folder 1040)
    - "N" General, 1931-1968 (Box 25, Folder 1041)
    - Nadejena, Lydia, undated (Box 25, Folder 1042)
    - Nannine, Joseph, 1934-1940 (Box 25, Folder 1043)
    - The Nation, 1932 February 26 (Box 25, Folder 1044)
    - Nemerov, Howard, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 1045)
    - Nevins, Allan, 1949, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 1046)
    - New American Library of World Literature, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 1047)
    - New England Quarterly, 1955-1969 (Box 25, Folder 1048)
    - New Haven Register, 1947-1949 (Box 25, Folder 1049)
    - New Haven State Teachers College, 1942 September 27 (Box 25, Folder 1050)
    - New Milford Public Library, 1942-1946 (Box 25, Folder 1051)
    - New York Central System, 1945 (Box 25, Folder 1052)
    - New York Herald, 1950 March 12 (Box 25, Folder 1053)
    - New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Company, 1945 May 1 (Box 25, Folder 1054)
    - New York Review of Books, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 1055)
    - New York Times Book Review, 1965-1972 (Box 25, Folder 1056)
    - New York Times Magazine, 1964 September 21 (Box 25, Folder 1057)
    - New York University, undated (Box 25, Folder 1058)
    - The New Yorker, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 1059)
    - Niebuhr, Richard R., 1961 January 17 (Box 25, Folder 1060)
    - Niebuhr, Reinhold, 1945-1953 (Box 25, Folder 1061)
    - Nivison, David, 1962-1963 (Box 25, Folder 1062)
    - Nivison, Ruth, 1961-1973 (Box 25, Folder 1063-1064)
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1970-1971 (Box 25, Folder 1065)
    - Nixseaman, Edith, 1961 April 1 (Box 25, Folder 1066)
    - Nolan, Charles J., 1979 (Box 25, Folder 1067)
    - Norton, Anne, undated (Box 25, Folder 1068)
    - Northrop, Connie R., undated (Box 25, Folder 1069)
    - Nunley, Richard, undated (Box 25, Folder 1070)
    - "O" General, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1071)
    - O----, Thomas F., 1936 (Box 26, Folder 1072)
    - Oakes, Clarence P., 1940 November 22 (Box 26, Folder 1073)
    - Ober, Beverly, 1939 October 25 (Box 26, Folder 1074)
    - Oberlin College, 1937-1939 (Box 26, Folder 1075)
    - O'Brien, W. Clyde, 1939 August 24 (Box 26, Folder 1076)
    - O'Conner, Hope, 1967 August 21 (Box 26, Folder 1077)
    - O'Connor, George M., 1961 November 15 (Box 26, Folder 1078)
    - Ogden, Archibald G., 1962 May 1 (Box 26, Folder 1079)
    - Oliver, Peter, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 1080)
    - Oliver, Robert, 1972 March 17 (Box 26, Folder 1081)
    - O'Neill, Eugene, 1926-1935 (Box 26, Folder 1082)
    - O'Neill, Rose, 1931 August 28 (Box 26, Folder 1083)
    - Oninger, Nelson, 1974 October 22 (Box 26, Folder 1084)
    - Opdyke, George H., 1932 December 7 (Box 26, Folder 1085)
    - Oppegard, Roy W., 1946 (Box 26, Folder 1086)
    - Oppel, Theodore W., 1934 October 14 (Box 26, Folder 1087)
    - Oppenheimer, David and Clare, 1964-1972 (Box 26, Folder 1088)
    - Oppenheimer, Richard, undated (Box 26, Folder 1089)
    - Ottemiller, John H., 1965 (Box 26, Folder 1090)
    - "P" General, 1933-1955, undated (Box 26, Folder 1091)
    - PEN (Organization), 1940-1971 (Box 26, Folder 1092-1093)
    - Packard, Sidney, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 1094)
    - Paddock, Edwin T., 1932 July 8 (Box 26, Folder 1095)
    - Padhye, M. R., 1955 (Box 26, Folder 1096)
    - Page, Elizabeth, 1941-1957 (Box 26, Folder 1097)
    - Page, Evelyn, 1928 (Box 26, Folder 1098)
    - Pamona College, 1948 July 8 (Box 26, Folder 1099)
    - Pangborn, Mark, 1968 June 14 (Box 26, Folder 1100)
    - Pantheon Books, Inc., 1959 (Box 26, Folder 1101)
    - Paquette, Don, 1934-1959 (Box 26, Folder 1102-1102a)
    - Paramount Pictures Inc., 1938 (Box 26, Folder 1103)
    - Pargellis, Stanley, 1949 (Box 26, Folder 1104)
    - Parker, Duryee, Benjamin, Zunino & Malone, 1955-1964 (Box 26, Folder 1105)
    - Parker, Lois Harger, 1948-1949 (Box 26, Folder 1106)
    - Parker, Richard, 1978 July 8 (Box 26, Folder 1107)
    - Parkhurst, Helen, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 1108)
    - Parks, Joseph, 1966-1969 (Box 26, Folder 1109)
    - Parrid, N., undated (Box 26, Folder 1110)
    - Parry, James, undated (Box 26, Folder 1111)
    - Parry, Honor and James, 1958-1965 (Box 26, Folder 1112)
    - Parsons, Edward L., undated (Box 26, Folder 1113)
    - Parsons, John C., 1935-1966 (Box 26, Folder 1114)
    - Empty folder, undated (Box 26, Folder 1115)
    - Patchen, Kenneth, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 1116)
    - Patterson, Frances, 1950 October 25 (Box 26, Folder 1117)
    - Pawling School, 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder 1118)
    - Pawling School Alumni Association, 1940 February 6 (Box 26, Folder 1119)
    - Pearson, Norman Holmes, 1950-1953 (Box 27, Folder 1120)
    - Pease, C. H., 1943 January 14 (Box 27, Folder 1121)
    - Peattie, Donald C., 1936 July 28 (Box 27, Folder 1122)
    - Peel, Robert, 1955 April 1 (Box 27, Folder 1123)
    - Perera, Charles, 1964-1968 (Box 27, Folder 1124)
    - Peterman, Rachel, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 1125)
    - Pettee, Frank, 1947 June 3 (Box 27, Folder 1126)
    - Perkins, H. A., 1940 November 24 (Box 27, Folder 1127)
    - Perkins, Max, 1932-1946 (Box 27, Folder 1128-1132)
      See also: Charles Scribners' Sons
    - Peter Franck - Hand Bookbinder, 1935 October 3 (Box 27, Folder 1133)
    - Peter Pauper Press, 1935-1936, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 1134)
    - Pfuetze, Paul, 1972 December (Box 27, Folder 1135)
    - Phelps, Charles, 1937-1938 (Box 27, Folder 1136)
    - Phelps, William Lyon, 1935-1940 (Box 27, Folder 1137)
    - The Phillips Exeter Academy, 1944 (Box 27, Folder 1138)
    - Ye Philosophic Publishing Company, 1929 November 12 (Box 27, Folder 1139)
    - Pickard, Darwin F., 1935 October 3 (Box 27, Folder 1140)
    - Pierce, Carolyn, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 1141)